const quizQuestions = [
   {
      question: "Sabaton is a band from Sweden, but from what city do they hail?",
      answerOptions: ["Lund", "Gothenburg", "Falun", "Stockholm"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   },
   {
      question: "How many studio albums does Sabaton band have?",
      answerOptions: [7, 9, 8, 10],
      correctAnswer: 1
   },
   {
      question: "Which song does describe a major World War II operation by the Polish Resistance home Army against Nazi Germany?",
      answerOptions: ["Final Solution", "Art Of War", "40:1", "Uprising"],
      correctAnswer: 3
   },

   {
      question: "Which song does describe a brave 77th US Division which was surrounded by the Germans in Argonne?",
      answerOptions: ["Winged Hussars", "82nd All The Way", "The Lost Batalion", "Last Dying Breath"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   },

   {
      question: "Which one of these music videos features a role by the Swedish actor Peter Stomare?",
      answerOptions: ["Uprising", "Screaming Eagles", "Ghost Division", "Cliffs Of Gallipoli"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   },

   {
      question: "What battle was centered around the song `Price Of A Mile` from the album `The Art of War`?",
      answerOptions: ["The Battle of Berlin", "The Battle of Kursk", "The Battle of Warsaw", "The Battle of Passchendaele"],
      correctAnswer: 3
   },

   {
      question: "'Pride of a nation, a beast made of steel!' the words from the following song",
      answerOptions: ["The Great War", "Bismarck", "Panzerkampf", "Ghost Division"],
      correctAnswer: 1
   },

   {
      question: "In which song an 'escape corridor' out of Berlin and a general of the 12th army who created it were glorified? ",
      answerOptions: ["Attero Dominatus", "The Red Baron", "Hearts Of Iron", "Rise Of Evil"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   },
   {
      question: "Who was the deadliest and the most dangerous sniper during WWI? ",
      answerOptions: ["Francis Pegahmagabow", "Noah Adamia", "Hiram Berdan", "Herman Davis"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   },

   {
      question: "Who did lead 16 men against the German defensive machine gun during the Meuse-Argonne Offensive",
      answerOptions: ["Frank Luke", "Noah Adamia", "Hiram Berdan", "Alvin York"],
      correctAnswer: 3
   },
   {
      question: "Which of these Sabaton albums was released in 2010?",
      answerOptions: ["Carolus Rex", "Coat of Arms ", "The Last Stand", "Heroes"],
      correctAnswer: 1
   },
   {
      question: "When did the winged hussars arrive?",
      answerOptions: ["12th of September, 1683", "9th of October, 1783 ", "12th of September, 1941", "15th of September, 1683"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   },
   {
      question: "What was the real name of soldier who served in 3 different armies?",
      answerOptions: ["Audie Murphy", "Leslie Allen", "Witold Pilecki", "Lauri Allan Törni"],
      correctAnswer: 3
   },

   {
      question: "What was the name of the soldier who faked his identity in order to be sent into jail?",
      answerOptions: ["Witold Pilecki", "Tadeusz Płużański", "Wilhelm Keitel", "Ryszard Jamontt-Krzywicki"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   },
   {
      question: "Which battle did take place on the 28th of June 1709 (Swedish calendar)?",
      answerOptions: ["The Battle of Narva", "Battle of Malplaquet", "The Battle of Poltava", "Battle of Almanza"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   },
   {
      question: "What was the name of the bomber from the song 'No Bullets Fly'?",
      answerOptions: ["B-24", "B-17", "Heinkel He 177", "Ilyushin II-4"],
      correctAnswer: 1
   },
   {
      question: "Who went to hell and came back?",
      answerOptions: ["Alvin York", "Witold Pilecki", "Karel Janoušek", "Audie Murphy"],
      correctAnswer: 3
   },

   {
      question: "Who did play a key role in the Battle of Britain?",
      answerOptions: ["Karel Janoušek", "Quintin Brand", "Simo Häyhä", "Lloyd Breadner"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   },
   {
      question: "Who was considered as ace-of-aces pilot-fighter during World War I with 80 confirmed allied kills to his name?",
      answerOptions: ["Ernst Udet", "Edward Mannock", "Manfred Albrecht Freiherr von Richthofen", "Rene Fonck"],
      correctAnswer: 2
   },
   {
      question: "When The Battle of Gallipoli took place?",
      answerOptions: ["between the 17th of February 1915 and the 9th of January 1916", "between the 17th of February 1914 and the 9th of January 1915", "1916", "1917"],
      correctAnswer: 0
   },
]
